Let's go home, Riko.
Riko?
Ok, job's done.
You're free to go now.
How were you able to get to this place?
What do you mean, Al?
Oh, I get what you're asking.
Gojo tried stopping me,
so I had to kill him.
Is that so? Die!
Don't be so impatient.
The season of the day What will
keep the same for the season?
The season of four sides.
The time of the day.
I'm in the middle of the
night. How many times?
As far as the wind.
It may be a much more.
You're in the middle of the day.
This day. This day.
If it's going to be a little.
This day.
Wherever you can get your smell,?
I don't know why you are alive.
I've been around forever.
Even though it's so hot.
Like a
snake,
It's so intense.
The tombs of the star in the Forbidden
Vault use barriers that conceal,
so they can't place
guards at the entrances.
As long as you know where the doors
are located, they're full of holes.
Sorcerers are busy
during this time of year,
and Jujutsu High is brimming
with flyheads right now.
It's pure chaos outside of here.
And since I have no cursed energy,
I'm like the Invisible Man.
There was one problem though.
If I wield a cursed tool
the cursed energy from
it will stop me from
being an invisible man!
There's more to this story?
See I keep a cursed spirit
around capable of storing objects
so that's where I usually
put my cursed tools.
You don't have to say it, though.
That means the cursed
energy from the cursed
spirit should stop me from
being an invisible man.
Can't have that.
So I make the cursed spirit small
enough to fit inside my body.
I keep it in my stomach.
After all, the organs of the invisible
man are invisible too, right?
That's how I'm able to pass
through any barrier while
still carrying all kinds
of cursed tools with me.
That's also why I didn't use a
cursed tool when I first got here.
Otherwise, I couldn't execute a
surprise attack on the Six Eyes.
Wouldn't be much of a surprise
if I wasn't invisible.
I could have killed the
Star Plasma vessel first,
but the risk of the Six
Eyes seeing me was too -
Enough!
You have a heavenly pact, right?
I know revealing info about your
abilities increases its strength,
just like for a sorcerer.
That's not what I want to know anyway.
How did you know which doors
led to the Tombs of the Star?
We didn't leave even the
slightest residuals behind.
Humans leave plenty of
traces aside from residuals.
Like scents, footprints, and so on.
My pact enhances all
five of my senses, too.
There should have been
another woman on the way here.
What happened to her?
Hmm?
Oh, that maid.
She's probably dead.
I didn't really care if she lived or died.
She's lucky she might still be alive.
Is that so?
You know, I really think you should die!
That Rainbow Dragon has
the toughest tide there is.
Curse manipulation.
A potential apparition deploys
a simple domain that enforces
non-violence on both of us
until I answer its question.
uh well i i'll just come out
and say it you're not my type.
so that's how it is huh?
hey it's over for you!
curse manipulation a
technique that lets me
absorb cursed spirits
that have surrendered.
and freely manipulate them if
there's roughly a two great
difference in our levels i skip
making them submit and absorb them
unconditionally his cursed spirit
may have a unique ability but it's
not that strong by itself i can absorb
it that'll lock down his armory.
Then I can just brute force it.
I didn't cut you badly enough to kill you.
Although, I would have killed
you if you were a Shikigami user.
But with curse manipulation,
there's no telling what
might happen to the
cursed spirits you've
absorbed after you die.
I'd rather avoid the
extra trouble if I can.
You have the blessing of parentage.
But, even with that blessing,
you were both beaten by a monkey like
me who can't even use curse techniques.
Yikes.
You wanna live a long
life, don't forget that.
Oh, speaking of blessings...
That's right, I almost forgot.
I gave him the name Megumi.
Go on now.
The corpse of the Star
Plasma Vessel, Riko Amanai.
All four limbs intact, too.
Hmm, indeed.
Indeed.
We'll issue your payment as we discussed.
I'll even throw in a bonus for you.
Thank you very much, Founder.
You're so generous.
He is not the Founder.
Huh?
Do you mean it?
I know it was a necessary expense,
but you've already helped us a lot.
I thought you'd complain a bit more.
We hired you for the assassination,
fully expecting it would fail.
Our star religious group
was founded in the Nara era,
when Tengen began preaching about the
moral foundations of Jujutsu sorcerers.
Jujutsu society and religious corporations
are at complete odds with each other.
That strain is what gave birth to
our modern star religious group,
the Time Vessel Association.
That is also why we have devoted
ourselves to remaining non-sorcerers.
Jujutsu Sorcerers are granted
many privileges above the law,
but they're still fundamentally
forbidden to lay hands on non-sorcerers.
However, the time had finally arrived.
The time of the taboo
recorded in our scriptures.
Our star religious group now
worships one absolute god.
And it was time for our object of
worship to assimilate with that impurity.
If we just sat back and let
the assimilation happen,
our association would
crumble yet if we took
excessive action jujutsu
sorcerers would crush us!
so we were truly desperate
to find an optimum
outcome and how did it
all turn out at first?
we thought we were going to
lose everything and now we
have it all a perfect reason
to loosen our purse strings?
what if tengen goes on
to lose control it could
very well turn out that
all of human society
will crumble if we
should perish along with
our star then that'll
be all there is to it?
were
you
referring
to okinawa
when you said they helped us?
yeah why didn't you kill the maid?
Right then, you had every chance to do it.
Don't you remember what I said?
Take her someplace far away and
then kill her at some point?
You wanna know why?
Because I had a pretty good idea of
what you were planning at the time.
I made the call that the relief
from the maid's successful rescue
would wear him down more than
heighten tensions from failure.
I knew you had an unfortunate
tendency to often ignore the
lines of communication and would
ignore whatever I was planning.
But it all worked out
in the end, didn't it?
And stop running your mediator ragged.
Fine.
But why did they help in Okinawa?
I had to laugh at that myself.
Normally, you'd use a car to
transport a captive, right?
Public transportation obviously
carries too many risks.
But check this out.
The president happens
to own a private jet.
Even so, asking for help...
Rich people think on a
different scale, man.
Yeah, well, let's go eat with their money.
Take me to one of those restaurants
that you use for clients.
Yeah, right, as if you're
gonna pick up the check for me.
Besides, I decided I'll
only see you again for work.
And if we don't work together
again, I guess I'll see you in hell.
Hey there it's been a
while huh are you for real
i'm for real real i'm
still alive and kicking.
Reverse curse technique
exactly when you stabbed
me through the throat i
gave up on counterattacking.
And poured all my focus
into the reverse curse
technique cursed energy
is negative energy while
It can enhance the body
it can't regenerate it so
you multiply that negative
energy against itself
To create positive
energy that's the reverse
curse technique easier said
than done i could never
do That till now and i
couldn't understand anything
the one something's off
he's blabbing on and on
Is he high but i finally grasped
it on the verge of death the
true essence of cursed energy The
reason you're going to lose is
because you didn't chop my head
off and because you didn't Use
that cursed tool when you stabbed
me in the head i'm gonna lose
Our fight is just getting started oh is
that right you could be
right you're so right
Curse technique reversal red
What a monster.
No bones are broken.
That shockwave was an
application of limitless.
The Cursed Technique Reversal Red, huh?
So he poured the positive
energy generated by the Reverse
Cursed Technique into the Limitless
Technique ingrained into him.
One, the power to stop the neutral
application of the Limitless Technique.
Two, the power to retract the amplified
application of the Limitless Technique Blue.
Three, the power to repel the
reversal of his Cursed Technique, Red.
All of these things I can handle,
but something's off.
Something's off.
Now, this is perfect.
You're dead!
Amanai, I'm sorry, but I have to admit,
I'm not even angry about you anymore.
I bear no crutch against anyone,
it's just that the world feels so,
so wonderful right now.
Throughout heaven and earth,
I alone am the honored one.
The merit of having a
technique that's passed
down for generations is
having a user's manual.
The downside is information about
the technique is easily leaked.
You were a member of the
Zenin clan, weren't you?
That's why you know so much
about the Limitless technique.
However, even in the Gojo clan, only
a scant few actually know about this.
Take the Amplified and the Reversal.
Then smash together those two different
infinities to create imaginary mass!
Imaginary Technique.
Hollow Purple.
Something's off.
I refuse to do any work for free.
Normally I would have said that
and hightailed it out of there.
Yet the freshly awakened wielder of the
limitless technique was
right before my eyes.
He was probably the strongest
jujutsu sorcerer of the modern age.
I wanted to reject him.
I wanted to bring him to his knees.
I wanted to take down the pinnacle of the
jujutsu world and the zenin
clan that rejected me.
I've twisted myself into knots for so
long, all to try justifying my life.
But that was the moment I truly lost.
I thought you had abandoned that pride.
I thought you had chosen to live
without respecting yourself.
Or anyone else for that matter?
Do you have any last words
that you would like to say?
Not really
Two or three years from now, my kid
will be sold off to the Zenin clan.
Do what you will with that.
I don't
know.
I don't know.
STM opponent, who is the guy named Soko?
The girl is in his way.
She wants to listen to him too.
He can be a man where he is.
She is so smart and can be a man.
The girl is home and has a man.
These are the four days
a day to stay alive.
Don't forget that they are home.
I have a family and I
don't work here with you.
I have a family, friends
and I have a family.
I love you.
To the people who they love me.
You're late, Suguru.
Actually, I guess you got here fast.
After all, there are several Star
Religious Group facilities in the city.
Satoru, is that you?
What happened?
I see you already saw Shoko.
Yeah, she was able to heal me.
I'm feeling fine again.
But that doesn't change
anything here, does it?
I screwed up pretty bad.
You're not the one at fault.
Let's head back.
Suguru, should we kill these guys?
The way I am right now, I
doubt I'd feel anything.
No.
There's no point.
It looks like they are
only common believers here.
The masterminds who know about our
world have probably fled already.
And unlike with the bounty, they won't
be able to talk their way out of this.
The organization had
problems to begin with.
It'll be dissolved soon enough.
No point, huh?
Does there really need
to be any point to it?
It's very important that there is,
especially for a Jujutsu Sorcerer.
I wonder if whoever
came up with the phrase,
a surprising side, thought
of people as cubes.
And if whoever came up with the insult,
shallow, thought of people as flat surfaces.
Next time, premature death.
Either way, people always
have two sides to them.